{
    "subject": "James_Cruze",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Marguerite_Snow",
    "human_readable": "James Cruze is married to Marguerite Snow.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883769154548645,
            "question": "Is Marguerite Snow married to James Cruze?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9624010324478149,
            "question": "Is there any information about Marguerite Snow besides her marriage to James Cruze?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9099813103675842,
            "question": "What is the relationship between James Cruze and Marguerite Snow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8889021873474121,
            "question": "Are James Cruze and Marguerite Snow in a romantic relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.876299262046814,
            "question": "Who is James Cruze married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6547056436538696,
            "question": "What is the name of James Cruze's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6289650201797485,
            "question": "What is the name of James Cruze's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6283998489379883,
            "question": "Who is Marguerite Snow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5417115688323975,
            "question": "Who shares a marital relationship with James Cruze?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39615899324417114,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the family of James Cruze?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Cruze is married to Marguerite Snow.",
            "html": "yago_10335_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital relationship with James Cruze?",
            "html": "yago_10335_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Marguerite Snow?",
            "html": "yago_10335_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of James Cruze's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_10335_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10335_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I found that:\n\n* The first document mentions \"Marguerite Snow and James Cruze were married for 10 years.\"\n* The second document lists James Cruze as a spouse of Marguerite Snow in her IMDb Mini Biography.\n* The third document does not explicitly mention their marriage, but it talks about Marguerite Snow being the wife of actor-turned-director James Cruze.\n\nTherefore, based on the provided context information, I conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"James Cruze is married to Marguerite Snow.\" The details in files like `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10335/re-ranker-msmarco/64.txt` and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10335/re-ranker-msmarco/50.txt` explicitly mention their marriage, indicating that they were indeed married to each other."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}